<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Owl Picks</title>
    <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Owl Picks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 13:20:49 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.owlpicks.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/patriots-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 13:20:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/patriots-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>The dynasty team finds its way into the playoffs yet again, this time as the second seed in the American Football Conference.
Quarterback: Tom Brady One year removed from being crowned the league MVP, Tom Brady is still very much an elite player. That being said, his play has regressed a bit. His deep ball accuracy percentage sunk downward from 46.5% to 43%. His passing yards per attempt has dropped by about three-tenths of a yard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/rams-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 11:36:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/rams-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>The Rams stumbled for a bit, but finally righted the ship at the end of the season to claim the second seed in the National Football Conference.
Quarterback: Jared Goff Some were making the case early in the season that Goff deserves serious MVP consideration. That case quickly went to shit after the Rams returned from their bye week. With defenses finally having decoded the Rams offensive scheme and Gurley banged up, Goff was largely left up to his own devices to create plays on the fly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/chiefs-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 17:13:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/chiefs-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>The Chiefs have emerged from nowhere and seized the top seed in the American Football Conference, thanks largely to the future MVP playing at quarterback - Patrick Mahomes.
Quarterback: Patrick Mahomes As the prospective MVP of the season, no question is Patrick Mahomes an elite quarterback.
Offensive Weapons: Tyreek Hill, Travis Kelce Tyreek Hill and Travis Kelce were spectacular last year, but even better this year now that a truly elite quarterback was at the helm of the offense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/saints-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 00:23:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/saints-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>New Orleans returns back to the postseason after a painful loss against the Vikings last year in the division round. The Saints stand as the top seed in the National Football Conference.
Quarterback: Drew Brees Drew Brees is an MVP candidate for a reason. Yes, a few of his games this season have been completely ordinary. But the eye test and the statistics irrefutably validates his status as an elite quarterback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/texans-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 00:07:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/texans-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Deshaun Watson&amp;rsquo;s return from ACL injury started out a little sloppy, to be honest. But once the team finally settled into a rhythm, the team won 11 of their last 14 contests, which netted them the 3rd seed in the American Football Conference.
Quarterback: Deshaun Watson The man truly earned his stripes this season. You see, for much of the season, Watson was forced to play without much talent in the receiver position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/eagles-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 23:49:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/eagles-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>With a little help from the Bears, the Eagles have slipped back into the playoffs as the bottom seed in the National Football Conference. Will Nick&amp;rsquo;s BD work its magic again this year?
Quarterback: Nick Foles / Nate Sudfeld Nick Foles seems like an elite quarterback. Watching film from yesterday&amp;rsquo;s game against the Redskins, I saw him looking off zone defenders, taking whatever opportunities were available to him, and throwing the ball with a little touch in order to hit his receivers in stride.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/bears-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 01:38:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/bears-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Under Matt Nagy, the Chicago Bears have gone from being considered the dregs of the NFC North division to being crowned the Kings of the North. Barring an unlikely loss by the Rams, Chicago is locked in as the third seed of the National Football Conference.
Quarterback: Mitchell Trubisky Mitch sucks. Not only is he horribly inaccurate, but some keen-eyed analysts have observed that the kid may simply be incapable of throwing the ball to the left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/seahawks-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/seahawks-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>The Seattle Seahawks are virtually locked into the fifth seed of the National Football Conference. Pretty amazing feat given their low preseason expectations&amp;hellip;
Quarterback: Russell Wilson Russell Wilson has been up and down this season. His performance against the Chiefs last week was a throwback to the last couple years when he was undoubtedly an elite quarterback. But then watch his game against the Vikings and doubts begin to creep up on whether he&amp;rsquo;s losing his touch&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/ravens-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 20:59:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/ravens-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>The Baltimore Ravens look likely for the 4th seed in the American Football Conference playoffs. And that seeding comes courtesy of their exciting rookie quarterback, Lamar Jackson.
Quarterback: Lamar Jackson As I&amp;rsquo;ll discuss at length in the next section, Lamar Jackson has been a jolt his team desperately needed after Joe Flacco went down with injury. But when it comes to executing on quarterbacking fundamentals&amp;hellip;the man disappoints. He&amp;rsquo;s not quite there yet as a pocket passer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/chargers-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 00:28:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/chargers-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>The ~Los Angeles~ San Diego Chargers are destined for the 5th seed in the American Football Conference playoffs. Despite a crummy home field advantage, the Bolts have rode high on some MVP-quality play from Philip Rivers.
Quarterback: Philip Rivers As I said before, Philip Rivers has played like an elite quarterback. There&amp;rsquo;s a reason his name has been thrown about in MVP discussions.
Offensive Weapons: Keenan Allen, Melvin Gordon It feels odd that the Chargers only have two solid offensive skill players, despite all their success in the passing game this season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>16</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/16/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 06:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/16/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>16</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/16/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 06:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/16/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/15/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 05:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/15/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/15/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 05:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/15/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>14</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 01:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/14/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>14</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 01:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/14/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>13</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 02:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/13/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>13</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 02:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/13/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving Bonanza!</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/thanksgiving-bonanza/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 22:08:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/thanksgiving-bonanza/</guid>
      <description>My favorite holiday of the year. Not because of the turkey or the food or anything, fuck that. It&amp;rsquo;s all about having the day off to make bets on three consecutive primetime football games.
Let&amp;rsquo;s look through each game and find some bets to like. I feel good about these slate of games too.
Chicago Bears @ Detroit Lions (+2.5) (Point Total: 43.5) The spread cleared below the key number of 3 earlier today as word finally got around that Mitch Trubisky was highly unlikely to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 05:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/12/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 05:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/12/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviewing Atlanta&#39;s Loss Against the Cowboys</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/reviewing-atlanta-s-loss-against-the-cowboys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 22:11:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/reviewing-atlanta-s-loss-against-the-cowboys/</guid>
      <description>To nudge myself out of the funk I was in Sunday night, when I barely missed hitting a lucrative five-team parlay (may the gods smite Kirk Cousins for the rest of his life), I decided to review game tape from the Falcons loss to the Cowboys earlier in the day.
Two major takeaways&amp;hellip;
 Matt Ryan found himself flustered by Dallas&amp;rsquo; pass rush, especially when they blitzed. His worst throws of the day came against blitzes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 11 - Risky Propositions</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-11-risky-propositions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 14:07:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-11-risky-propositions/</guid>
      <description>In this series, I&amp;rsquo;ll details bets that are a little risky for my blood.
Panthers @ Lions Such a beautiful spot for the Lions here. Coming off three embarrassing losses, Detroit is primed to play better now that they&amp;rsquo;ve returned back home and their season is on the line. And last week&amp;rsquo;s game against Chicago shows me that the team can defend against the run when it&amp;rsquo;s a central focus of their defensive game plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 11 Best Bets</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-11-best-bets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 21:58:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-11-best-bets/</guid>
      <description>All right, so the Supercontest is a lost cause. I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure I&amp;rsquo;m treading water at exactly 50%. Statistically, I&amp;rsquo;m no better than a coin. A fucking coin.
But at the very least, each season offers up lessons for me to internalize. I like to believe I improve as a bettor every year. To be honest though, my best year as a sports gambler has been the first year I&amp;rsquo;ve actually started wagering serious money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 03:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/11/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 03:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/11/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 10 Bets</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-10-bets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 14:52:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-10-bets/</guid>
      <description>Good week last week from a betting perspective, even if two of my Supercontest picks were losers. A superteaser hit landed me a pretty penny. Anyway&amp;hellip;
Saints (-6) @ Bengals Give me the Saints all day long.
The Bengals biggest problem on offense has always been that they lack reliable weapons that have won over the trust of their quarterback, Andy Dalton. And now you tell me his most trusted receiver in AJ Green is out?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bucs @ Panthers - Some Quick Game Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/bucs-panthers-some-quick-game-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 20:58:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/bucs-panthers-some-quick-game-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Just some real quick analysis&amp;hellip;.
The Panthers played phenomenal here, much to my surprise. And yet, a part of me still has questions of whether the Panthers are actually a legitimate playoff threat.
Their success in the last game was predicated on two things - devilishly creative play-calling and an eagerness to blitz against an offense that has absolutely no ability to read an incoming blitz.
Don&amp;rsquo;t believe me? Well, let me show you a few plays that stood out to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 03:38:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/10/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 03:38:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/10/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 9 - Sunday Night Football</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-9-sunday-night-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 18:00:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-9-sunday-night-football/</guid>
      <description>Packers (+5) @ Patriots Listen, it&amp;rsquo;s always risky betting against the Patriots, but their defense is a little too tepid for my liking. The Packers will cover so long as Bill Belichick&amp;rsquo;s defense fail to keep Aaron Rodger&amp;rsquo;s receivers bottled up under man coverage. As I keep saying, the Packers can be routed so long as you have a defensive secondary that can hold up well in man-to-man defense. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have such a secondary, expect Rodgers to run up some scores on you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 9 - Best Bets</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-9-best-bets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 23:43:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-9-best-bets/</guid>
      <description>My best bets of the week. Last week, I went 2-3. Two of those three losses came courtesy of the Chiefs and Rams failing to cover their spreads. BAH! I would not consider either of those picks to be terrible&amp;hellip;but it is pretty clear neither team deserved to cover their respective spreads last week. And this week, I will be rooting against one of them to flat out lose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/9/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 03:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/9/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/9/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 03:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/9/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 8 Review</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-8-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 22:26:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-8-review/</guid>
      <description>My Supercontest picks sucked this week.
Not really too interested in dwelling too much on why my selections didn&amp;rsquo;t pan out, although I do want to give a bit of a breakdown of the Kansas City/Denver game.
As I expected, Kansas City would post at least 30 points. But what took me by surprise was Case Keenum. Arrowhead Stadium is usually the place where bad quarterbacks go to finally die. Just look at Blake Bortles and his downfall following his poor showing in Arrowhead earlier in the season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 23:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/8/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 23:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/8/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 8 - Early Leanings</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-8-early-leanings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 20:12:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-8-early-leanings/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 02:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/7/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 02:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/7/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 7 - Early Leanings</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-7-early-leanings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 22:57:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-7-early-leanings/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>49ers @ Packers - Quick Look</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/49ers-packers-quick-look/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 20:01:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/49ers-packers-quick-look/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rams-Broncos Halftime Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/rams-broncos-halftime-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 17:43:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/rams-broncos-halftime-analysis/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colts @ Jets - Halftime Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/colts-jets-halftime-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 14:26:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/colts-jets-halftime-analysis/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 05:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/6/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 05:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/6/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 5 Picks</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-5-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 22:30:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-5-picks/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 02:06:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/5/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 01:07:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/5/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 4 Picks</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-4-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 00:25:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-4-picks/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction...</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 22:24:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 18:25:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/4/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 18:25:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/4/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 01:16:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 01:06:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 22:34:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 23:50:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 23:27:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/elo/1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 05:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/games/1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>