<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Owl Picks</title>
    <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Owl Picks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/postseason-review-saints/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/postseason-review-saints/</guid>
      <description>The Saints oddly only the 3rd seed in the NFC due to some unfortunate luck when Drew Brees injured his thumb against the Rams and an underprepared Teddy Bridgewater had to step into his place. Even still, New Orleans has been billed as one of the favorites to win. Let&amp;rsquo;s use the the rubric here to see exactly why.
Is the team mentally tough? No doubt. Winning five straight games without Drew Brees alone proves the team can handle hardship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/postseason-review-texans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/postseason-review-texans/</guid>
      <description>The Texans have limped into the playoffs as the fourth seed in the AFC. Let&amp;rsquo;s use the rubric here to see if they can go far in the postseason.
Is the team mentally tough? No doubt. Winning five straight games without Drew Brees alone proves the team can handle hardship. Their comeback win against a surging Titans team in Tennessee is another fine example that exemplifies this team&amp;rsquo;s mental fortitude.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/postseason-review-eagles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/postseason-review-eagles/</guid>
      <description>The Eagles have managed to win the NFC East after so much drama. Let&amp;rsquo;s see if they can actually survive a game or two though. We&amp;rsquo;ll evaluate them using the rubric here.
Is the team mentally tough? Yes. It&amp;rsquo;s been painful watching the Eagles this year, but these past few weeks have shown me Philadelphia has demonstrated enough resilience and grit to be considered mentally tough. It takes some fortitude to survive games the past two weeks while so many people on your roster are going down like flies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/postseason-review-seahawks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/postseason-review-seahawks/</guid>
      <description>The Seahawks are returning to the playoffs once again as a wild card team. Let&amp;rsquo;s see if their fortunes will be better this year using my lovely little rubric here.
Is the team mentally tough? Yes. Once again returning to this idea that mental fortitude is primarily a function of the head coach, I&amp;rsquo;d be remiss to doubt Pete Carroll and the attitude that he instills in his team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/postseason-review-patriots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/postseason-review-patriots/</guid>
      <description>The Patriots are seeing Wild Card weekend for the first time in over ten years, shockingly. So let&amp;rsquo;s examine their prospects using my trusty old rubric here.
Is the team mentally tough? One would think so going solely off history. But in reality, this team shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have lost the way it did against the Dolphins last week. It was an embarrassing loss to a team listed as double-digit underdogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/postseason-review-titans/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/postseason-review-titans/</guid>
      <description>A resurgent Titans squad led by Ryan Tannehill has muscled their way into the playoffs. Let&amp;rsquo;s look at their playoff prospects using the rubric outlined here.
Is the team mentally tough? Yes, sufficiently so. After benching their franchise quarterback for a burn-out from Miami, one would be forgiven for thinking the Titans were done for the season. Instead, their fortunes swung upward - the team found renewed life with a quarterback that wasn&amp;rsquo;t afraid to lob the ball into smaller, riskier windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/postseason-review-bills/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/postseason-review-bills/</guid>
      <description>The Buffalo Bills have fought their way into the playoffs for the second time under Sean McDermott. Now let&amp;rsquo;s review them using the rubric defined here.
Is the team mentally tough? Yes, the team is mentally tough. They&amp;rsquo;ve done enough to demonstrate a will to fight, winning almost all the games they&amp;rsquo;re supposed to win. Their defense has hung in their in tough moments, defending leads against last-minute comeback attempts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/postseason-review-minnesota-vikings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/postseason-review-minnesota-vikings/</guid>
      <description>Using the rubric outlined here, it&amp;rsquo;s time for us to start our review of postseason teams with the sixth seed of the NFC, the Minnesota Vikings!
Is the team mentally tough? No. It&amp;rsquo;s hard for me to say this too, as I always respected Mike Zimmer and the defenses that he trains up. His defenses are usually greater than the sum of their parts. But the offense is nowhere near as resilient as the defense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/postseason-review-team-assessment-rubric/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/postseason-review-team-assessment-rubric/</guid>
      <description>So in assessing these teams and figuring out which teams are more likely to perform well compared to others, I need to come up with some sort of guide that can help me compare these clubs against one another. Yes I know that any one model will fail to grasp all the finer details of the game that motivate the final result, but I do genuinely feel that a great model can be right so much more often than wrong, especially in the playoffs when seasonal data points are pretty much stable at the point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-17-quick-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-17-quick-insights/</guid>
      <description>49ers @ Seahawks On the first drive, the 49ers defensive line won all their battles at the line of scrimmage. Arik Armstead and Nick Bosa have been impressive in particular.
The 49ers have some fantastic options on offense. George Kettle, Deebo Samuel, Emmanuel Sanders, Kyle Juscyzk, Raheem Mostert, and Matt Breida are all dependable vectors on offense.
More aggressive press coverage being played by the 49ers against these Seahawks. Impressive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-16-quick-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-16-quick-insights/</guid>
      <description>Texans @ Buccaneers Jameis getting steadily better, though his turnover rate is still ridiculous.
Texans still have no viable pass rush without JJ Watt.
Houston actually has some quality pass coverage personnel, though this is Jameis we&amp;rsquo;re talking about. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how they perform against actual competition come playoff time.
Bills @ Patriots Bills are being gashed on the ground for steady yardage.
Some creative play-calling by the Patriots offense, throwing a ball to N&amp;rsquo;Keal Harry running a wheel route after play action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-15-quick-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-15-quick-insights/</guid>
      <description>Buccaneers @ Lions Josh Wells a liability as a replacement left tackle for Tampa Bay.
Detroit Lions actually blitzed for once and managed to secure an interception off that blitz.
The Lions are so bad in their defensive backfield, I love it.
Bears @ Packers The Packers truly have one of the best offensive lines in the league. Their pass-blocking and run-blocking has been stellar this week and last week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-15-supercontest-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-15-supercontest-picks/</guid>
      <description>Buccaneers @ Lions (+3) It&amp;rsquo;s hard for me to trust Jameis here, especially given that he&amp;rsquo;s without his favorite weapon in Mike Evans. Still, Jameis did all right last week when Evans had to leave early. Things would have been much better if he didn&amp;rsquo;t throw three ugly interceptions against the Colts and their zone defense.
It helps that the Lions almost exclusively play man coverage here, as it limits opportunities for interceptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-14-quick-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-14-quick-insights/</guid>
      <description>49ers @ Saints As expected, the Saints are working the 49ers in the short game, as the Cardinals did not too long ago.
Absence of Jaquiski Tartt at deep safety made a difference on an intermediate throw to Jared Cook for a touchdown.
49ers picking on Eli Apple on three consecutive downs for big plays. Eli Apple seems to have a hard time guarding the slant.
49ers coming into this game well-coached and ready, given the success of their first drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-14-supercontest-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-14-supercontest-picks/</guid>
      <description>Ravens @ Bills (+5.5) The Bills&amp;rsquo; big win against Dallas may have been overblown, given Chicago&amp;rsquo;s manhandling of the Cowboys last night.
But more important than that, the Bills still have a major problem guarding against the run. While they&amp;rsquo;ve improved a little over the past few weeks, it&amp;rsquo;s a problem that&amp;rsquo;s going to linger for the whole season. And that weakness will be exposed in the worst possible way against a Ravens team that can run the ball a myriad of ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-13-supercontest-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-13-supercontest-picks/</guid>
      <description>Browns @ Steelers (+2) I can&amp;rsquo;t help but feel that the Brownies are walking straight into a trap here. Coming off a big win, facing off against a team that it just dominated a few weeks ago (which is now starting a third-stringer at quarterback, mind you)&amp;hellip;the reasons are there to phone this game in, especially with Freddie Kitchens&amp;rsquo; lackadaisical coaching.
The Steelers, on the other hand, should be hyped for this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-13-quick-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-13-quick-insights/</guid>
      <description>Bears @ Lions The Lions suck. Just something worth noting.
The Bears seem to suck more though. This new quarterback Brough is actually stepping up and making good plays in Chicago&amp;rsquo;s loose zone coverage. Did the Bears&amp;rsquo; defensive backfield come into this match not giving a shit?
The Lions suck, particularly up front. Their pass rush is virtually nonexistant. Despite the Lions&amp;rsquo; hot start, the Bears have posted more yards on offense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-12-quick-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-12-quick-insights/</guid>
      <description>Giants @ Bears Trubisky plays much better in a high-tempo offense.
Cowboys @ Patriots The Patriots will need to commit more to running the ball, as their passing game is still a mess when throws are not schemed.
Cowboys have seen some success running the ball. Nothing too consistent, but it seems like something that&amp;rsquo;ll help them string a few plays together on a scoring drive.
These Cowgirls aren&amp;rsquo;t equipped to play in wet and windy conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-12-supercontest-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-12-supercontest-picks/</guid>
      <description>Broncos @ Bills (-4) A bit of a risky pick given that the Broncos can run the ball behind Philip Lindsay and the offensive coaching staff has shown a penchant for trickery, but this Bills defense is overall much better than a Broncos offense led by a quarterback that has yet to show he can play dropback football.
Plus the injuries along the Broncos offensive line should present pass-rushing opportunities for this Bills front seven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-11-quick-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-11-quick-insights/</guid>
      <description>Texans @ Ravens Matthew Judon dominating against the run and at taking down the quarterback.
Deshaun Watson seems to be leaning too heavily on DeAndre Hopkins in the passing game. Lots of slants and even a deep heave in his direction on a critical 4th down play.
Ravens&amp;rsquo; defensive line has been a little sloppy with their aggressiveness. One bad penalty sustained an ultimately fruitless Texans drive.
Houston&amp;rsquo;s pass rush is nonexistent, as expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-11-supercontest-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-11-supercontest-picks/</guid>
      <description>Saints @ Buccaneers (+5.5) Not the biggest fan of taking road favorites, but the Saints are coming off a horrific loss to an opponent that really had no standing to beat them. New Orleans clearly lost focus coming off the bye. That focus should be in place after the loss.
Now cue this game against the Buccaneers. As I noted before, Tampa Bay has a tendency to struggle against division opponents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-10-quick-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-10-quick-insights/</guid>
      <description>Bills @ Browns Finally, Baker is re-establishing a rapport with Jarvis Landry.
Three downs to move the ball one yard in order to keep the chains moving. Kitchens opts for three straight passing plays, despite having one of the best halfbacks in the game. Only on the fourth down do you try play action. Amazing.
Cleveland&amp;rsquo;s offensive line cannot play power football. Six rushes roughly three or less yards away from the goal line and the Browns were hopeless on just about every single run, especially against a team that has not been so stout against the rush.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-10-supercontest-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-10-supercontest-picks/</guid>
      <description>Cardinals @ Buccaneers (-4.5) A little wary of this pick, as Tampa Bay tends to play better against non-division opponents. And really, the Buccaneers should have covered last week against Seattle, which means this spread should be a touch higher.
Still&amp;hellip;Arizona has been remarkably competent over the past couple weeks. Kliff Kingsbury&amp;rsquo;s willingness to tweak his air raid philosophy over the past few weeks and incorporate more rushing plays into the offensive playbook has paid off in spades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-9-quick-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-9-quick-insights/</guid>
      <description>Texans @ Jaguars (London) Leonard Fournette being a power runner doesn&amp;rsquo;t bode well for a Jaguars team playing from behind.
Remind me to never side with a rookie quarterback in his second outing against a division opponent. The Texans are not getting any pressure on Minshew, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to matter as Houston seems to have gotten a beat on the Jaguars passing tendencies. The Texans&amp;rsquo; coverage schemes are taking away many of the offensive concepts Minshew has gotten comfortable executing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-9-supercontest-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-9-supercontest-picks/</guid>
      <description>Texans @ Jaguars (+1) I have faith in Gardner Minshew and the Jaguars offense finding some success here in their second home against a Texans defense missing its best playmaker in J.J. Watt.
I am worried about the Jaguars and their porous coverage schemes here. Their soft zone defense can be picked apart by good quarterbacks. And given Watson&amp;rsquo;s ability to run the ball, that would expose this questionable defense even more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-8-quick-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-8-quick-insights/</guid>
      <description>Giants @ Lions Why does Pat Shurmur run on 2nd and long? Why is this a thing in the NFL?
Giants run defense once again choking up yardage to opposing rushers.
Jones is rough. The kid is still holding on to balls recklessly. And Shurmur telegraphing run plays doesn&amp;rsquo;t help the situation.
Giants offensive playbook seems to favor high-low routes where a receiver runs a slant route to the outside while the inside receiver crosses underneath to the flat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-7-quick-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-7-quick-insights/</guid>
      <description>Cardinals @ Giants Chase Edmonds is a beast at halfback. Good vision and acceleration.
Cardinals are actually incorporating a good number of run plays into their offensive playbooks. Some balance is being maintained here, which is telling. It honestly seems Kingsbury&amp;rsquo;s Air Raid experiment may have come to an end here. Even though no team runs more 10 personnel sets than the Cardinals, the fact that Arizona is willfully running the ball on a regular basis violates one of the core tenets of the Air Raid philosophy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-7-supercontest-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-7-supercontest-picks/</guid>
      <description>Patriots @ Jets (+9.5) It&amp;rsquo;s hard going against the Patriots here, but give me a Jets team that found a second life with the return of Sam Darnold last week. It also helps that C.J. Mosley should be coming back into the fold here after spending the last several weeks sidelined with injury.
Besides, it helps that New York&amp;rsquo;s coaches should be better prepared in this match, having faced off against New England just a few weeks ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-6-quick-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-6-quick-insights/</guid>
      <description>Seahawks @ Browns The Browns are just hot garbage, starting with Baker Mayfield.
To start, Baker threw two passes behind his receivers that ended up being picked. He also threw another interception early in the game that stunted some of the momentum the Browns built up out of the gate. Nick Chubb also fumbled the ball on another critical drive during the second half.
The coaching on a Browns drive that ended at the Seahawks goal line was atrocious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-6-supercontest-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-6-supercontest-picks/</guid>
      <description>49ers @ Rams (-3) It&amp;rsquo;s a little alarming to me that the books consider the 49ers and the Rams as (more or less) equal. One team has a better quarterback than the other. And that should make the difference here, more or less.
I see Wade Phillips stacking the box in order to stop the run game. Sure, his defensive backs will be left on their own against the 49ers&amp;rsquo; skill players, but that&amp;rsquo;s a gamble I&amp;rsquo;m sure Wade is willing to take.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-5-quick-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-5-quick-insights/</guid>
      <description>Vikings @ Giants Zimmer cannot still shake off his pathological conservative nature on offense. On a 3rd &amp;amp; 20 play in the red zone, Zimmer opted for the shotgun draw.
Jabrill Peppers has been beastly against the run today.
Giants zone defense is simply lousy, as expected.
Dalvin Cook is something special.
Daniel Jones seems to genuinely enjoy throwing outside the numbers, even against tight coverage. The Giants need more X-style receivers that could catch those contested balls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-4-quick-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-4-quick-insights/</guid>
      <description>Jaguars @ Broncos Jaguar linebackers not playing disciplined against misdirection plays.
Jacksonville doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to have much of a red zone playbook.
Jalen Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s understudy not doing all too well. But in his defense, the Broncos were able to move the ball on him thanks largely to some well-drawn plays.
Those plays involved wide receivers running crossing routes on third down in order to create space for a halfback coming out of the backfield, running play-action off a heavy formation, and then motioning a tailback away from the pocket in order to create a throwing lane up the seam for Flacco.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-3-quick-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-3-quick-insights/</guid>
      <description>Titans @ Jaguars The Jaguars insist on running a zone coverage scheme that forces their linebackers to run around the field and even blanket receivers at times. It&amp;rsquo;s not good when Jacksonville has a slow bunch of linebackers outside of Myles Jack.
Jacksonville is still trying to build an offensive identity around Leonard Fournette instead of the passing game. The Titans are keying in on Fournette though, stalling the Jaguars anemic offense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-3-supercontest-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-3-supercontest-picks/</guid>
      <description>Ravens @ Chiefs (-6.5) I initially sides with the Ravens here, especially as 7-point underdogs. But a bit more probing into this match-up and I uncovered a few things that worried me. One, Lamar Jackson is playing almost too well as a passer given his performance from last year. The man is due for regression soon, and what better place to regress than a stadium famed for exposing quarterbacks playing far above their pay grade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-2-quick-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-2-quick-insights/</guid>
      <description>Bills @ Giants The Bills&amp;rsquo; man coverage is real.
The Giants&amp;rsquo; man coverage is lame though. DeAndre Baker is a particular point of weakness.
If it wasn&amp;rsquo;t for some early runs from Saquon Barkley and slant routes, the Giants offense would have been complete rudderless.
Josh Allen is committing to staying in the pocket. Though it&amp;rsquo;s easy to do so considering New York&amp;rsquo;s gutless pass rush.
49ers @ Bengals Kwan Alexander is quite passionate and embraces the leadership role he&amp;rsquo;s been given on defense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-2-supercontest-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-2-supercontest-picks/</guid>
      <description>49ers @ Bengals (-2.0) Kind of weird for me to go with a team that I ranked as a dreg-tier team before the season. But Cincinnati truly impressed me last week, going up to the Clink to face off against a Seattle defense that prepped well for a McVay-style offense. Instead, the Bengals offense seems to have developed its own identity, one that suits Andy Dalton from what I saw last week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-1-quick-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-1-quick-insights/</guid>
      <description>Chiefs @ Jaguars The one team unable to handle the humidity in Jacksonville today were&amp;hellip;the Jaguars. How? It seemed like the Kansas City players were having a merry old time playing out there in the searing heat while the Jaguars defenders were looking exhausted by the second quarter. How the hell is this even possible? Did these Jaguars never once practice outside during training camp? I just don&amp;rsquo;t get it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-49ers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 12:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-49ers/</guid>
      <description>Tier 6 QB: Jimmy Garoffalo
Known Offensive Vectors: George Kittle (TE), Kyle Juszczyk (FB), Tevin Coleman (RB), Marquise Goodwin (WR)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Jordan Matthews (WR)
Key Defensive Personnel: DeForest Buckner (DT), Dee Ford (DE), Nick Bosa (DE), Kwon Alexander (LB), Richard Sherman (CB), Jason Verrett (CB)
Managers: John Lynch (GM), Kyle Shanahan (HC/OC), Robert Saleh (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 8
Coaching Turnover:
On offense, we see a bit of organization and the hiring of even more coaches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-cardinals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 12:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-cardinals/</guid>
      <description>Tier 6 QB: Kyler Murray
Known Offensive Vectors: Christian Kirk (WR), David Johnson (RB), Kyler Murray (Mobile QB)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Larry Fitzgerald (WR)
Key Defensive Personnel: Chandler Jones (DE), Terrell Suggs (OLB), Jordan Hicks (ILB), Patrick Peterson (CB), Budda Baker (S)
Managers: Steve Keim (GM), Kliff Kingsbury (New HC), Tom Clements (New OC), Vance Joseph (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 5
Coaching Turnover:
With the exception of a few assistant coaches, the entire coaching staff has been flipped from the top-down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-rams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 12:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-rams/</guid>
      <description>Tier 3 QB: Jared Goff
Known Offensive Vectors: Todd Gurley (RB), Robert Woods (WR), Cooper Kupp (WR)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Brandin Cooks (WR)
Key Defensive Personnel: Aaron Donald (DT), Clay Matthews (DE), Marcus Peters (CB), Aqib Talib (CB), Eric Weddle (FS), Taylor Rapp (SS)
Managers: Les Snead (GM), Sean McVay (HC/OC), Wade Phillips (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 10.5
Coaching Turnover:
Zac Taylor, last year’s quarterbacks coach, left to become head coach of the Bengals,.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-seahawks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 12:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-seahawks/</guid>
      <description>Tier 2 QB: Russell Wilson
Known Offensive Vectors: Russell Wilson (Mobile QB), Tyler Lockett (WR), Chris Carson (RB), Will Dissly (TE)
Potential Offensive Vectors: N/A
Key Defensive Personnel: Jadeveon Clowney (DE), Ezekiel Ansah (DE), L.J. Collier (DE), Jarran Reed (DT), Bobby Wagner (LB), Bradley McDougald (SS)
Managers: John Schneider (GM), Pete Carroll (HC), Brian Schottenheimer (OC), Ken Norton Jr (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 8.5
Coaching Turnover:
On offense, the team added a few more assistants to the staff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-panthers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-panthers/</guid>
      <description>Tier 7 QB: Cam Newton
Known Offensive Vectors: Christian McCaffrey (RB), Curtis Samuel (WR)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Greg Olsen (TE), D.J. Moore (WR)
Notable Defensive Personnel: Kawann Short (DT), Luke Kuechly (MLB), Brian Burns (LB), Shaq Thompson (OLB), Eric Reid (FS)
Managers: Marty Hurney (GM), Ron Rivera (HC), Norv Turner (OC), Eric Washington (DC)
Vegas over/Under: 7.5
Coaching Turnover:
On offense, things have mostly remained the same, save for the wide receivers coach and the running backs coach being new this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-falcons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 12:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-falcons/</guid>
      <description>Tier 3 QB: Matt Ryan
Known Offensive Vectors: Julio Jones (WR), Calvin Ridley (WR), Austin Hooper (TE)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Devonta Freeman (RB), Mohamed Sanu (WR)
Notable Defensive Personnel: Grady Jarrett (DT), Tak McKinley (DE), Deion Jones (MLB), Keanu Neal (SS), Desmond Trufant (CB)
Managers: Thomas Dimitroff (GM), Dan Quinn (HC/New DC), Dirk Koetter (New OC),
Vegas Over/Under: 9.5
Staff Turnover:
The turnover here is complicated.
Dirk Koetter was brought in to take charge of the offense after the higher powers in Atlanta fired Steve Sarkisian following his shaky mismanagement of the offense last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-saints/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 12:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-saints/</guid>
      <description>Tier 1 QB: Drew Brees
Known Offensive Vectors: Michael Thomas (WR), Alvin Kamara (RB), Jared Cook (TE)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Tre’Quan Smith (WR), Ted Ginn Jr (WR)
Key Defensive Personnel: Cameron Jordan (DE), Marcus Davenport (DE), Demario Davis (OLB), Sheldon Rankins (DT), Marshon Lattimore (CB), Eli Apple (CB)
Managers: Mickey Loomis (GM), Sean Payton (HC), Pete Carmichael (OC), Dennis Allen (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 10.5
Staff Turnover:
No significant turnover on either side of the ball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-buccaneers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 12:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-buccaneers/</guid>
      <description>Tier 4 QB: Jameis Winston
Known Offensive Vectors: Mike Evans (WR), O.J. Howard (TE),
Potential Offensive Vectors: Chris Godwin (WR), Breshad Perriman (WR), Peyton Barber (RB)
Key Defensive Personnel: Ndamukong Suh (DT), Jason Pierre-Paul (OLB),
Managers: Jason Licht (GM), Bruce Arians ( New HC), Byron Leftwich (New OC), Todd Bowles (New DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 6.5
Staff Turnover:
The entire offensive coaching staff has been revamped under new head coach, Bruce Arians.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-bears/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 12:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-bears/</guid>
      <description>Tier 6 QB: Mitch Trubisky
Known Offensive Vectors: Mitch Trubisky (Mobile QB), Tarik Cohen (RB)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Allen Robinson (WR), Cordarrelle Patterson (WR)
Key Defensive Personnel: Akeem Hicks (DT), Khalil Mack (DE), Kyle Fuller (CB), Roquan Smith (LB), Danny Trevathan (LB), Buster Skrine (CB), Prince Amukamara (CB)
Managers: Ryan Pace (GM), Matt Nagy (HC), Mark Helfrich (OC), Chuck Pagano (New DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 9.5
Coaching Turnover:
On offense, the staff has remained fully intact, with the addition of Brad Childress as an advisor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-lions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 12:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-lions/</guid>
      <description>Tier 7 QB: Matthew Stafford
Known Offensive Vectors: Kenny Golladay (WR)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Kerryon Johnson (RB), Marvin Jones (WR), Danny Amendola (WR), T.J. Hockenson (TE)
Key Defensive Personnel: Darius Slay (CB), Trey Flowers (DE), Damon Harrison (DT), Mike Daniels (DT)
Managers: Bob Quinn (GM), Matt Patricia (HC), Darrell Bevell (New OC), Paul Pasqualoni (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 6.5
Coaching Turnover:
Despite hiring a new offensive coordinator to helm the offense, the Lions didn’t flip much at the position group level, only replacing the coaches overseeing the quarterbacks and running backs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-vikings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 12:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-vikings/</guid>
      <description>Tier 2 QB: Kirk Cousins
Known Offensive Vectors: Adam Thielen (WR), Stefon Diggs (WR), Dalvin Cook (RB)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Kyle Rudolph (TE), Ameer Abdullah (RB), Chad Beebe (WR)
Key Defensive Personnel: Everson Griffen (DE), Danielle Hunter (DE), Linval Joseph (DT), Anthony Barr (LB), Anthony Kendricks (LB), Harrison Smith (SS), Xavier Rhodes (CB)
Managers: Rick Spielman (GM), Mike Zimmer (HC), Kevin Stefanski/Gary Kubiak (New OC), George Edwards (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 9</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-packers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-packers/</guid>
      <description>Tier 5 QB: Aaron Rodgers
Known Offensive Vectors: Davante Adams (WR), Aaron Rodgers (Mobile QB)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Aaron Jones (RB), Jimmy Graham (TE)
Key Defensive Personnel: Za’Darius Smith (DT/LB), Preston Smith (OLB), Rashan Gary (OLB), Adrian Amos (SS), Jaire Alexander (CB)
Managers: Brian Gutekunst (GM), Matt LaFleur (New HC), Nathaniel Hackett (New OC), Mike Pettine (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 9
Coaching Turnover:
On offense, only the running backs coach from last year managed to survive the Packers’ transition away from the Mike McCarthy era.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-redskins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 12:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-redskins/</guid>
      <description>Tier 8 QB: Case Keenum, Dwayne Haskins
Known Offensive Vectors: N/A
Potential Offensive Vectors: Jordan Reed (TE), Vernon Davis (TE), Josh Doctson (WR), Adrian Peterson (RB)
Key Defensive Personnel: Matt Ioannidis (DE), Montez Sweat (OLB), Ryan Kerrigan (OLB), Landon Collins (SS), Josh Norman (CB)
Managers: Bruce Allen (GM/Exec), Jay Gruden (HC), Kevin O’Connell (New OC), Greg Manusky (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 6
Coaching Turnover:
On offense, we have a peculiar situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-giants/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 12:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-giants/</guid>
      <description>Tier 7 QB: Eli Manning, Daniel Jones
Known Offensive Vectors: Sterling Shepard (WR), Saquon Barkley (RB), Golden Tate (WR)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Evan Engram (TE)
Key Defensive Personnel: Janoris Jenkins (CB), Michael Thomas (FS), Jabrill Peppers (SS), Dalvin Tomlinson (DT)
Managers: Dave Gettleman (GM), Pat Shurmur (HC), Mike Shula (OC), James Bettcher (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 6
Coaching Turnover:
The Giants have kept their whole offensive coaching staff from last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-cowboys/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 12:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-cowboys/</guid>
      <description>Tier 4 QB: Dak Prescott
Known Offensive Vectors: Ezekiel Elliott (RB), Amari Cooper (WR)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Dak Prescott (Mobile QB), Randall Cobb (WR), Jason Witten (TE), Dak Prescott (Mobile QB)
Key Defensive Personnel: Demarcus Lawrence (DE), Robert Quinn (DE), Leighton Vander Esch (OLB), Jaylon Smith (MLB), Byron Jones (CB), Chidobe Awuzie (CB)
Managers: Jerry Jones (GM), Jason Garrett (HC), Kellen Moore (New OC), Rod Marinelli (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 9</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-eagles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-eagles/</guid>
      <description>Tier 1 QB: Carson Wentz
Known Offensive Vectors: Zach Ertz (TE), Alshon Jeffery (WR), DeSean Jackson (WR), Miles Sanders (RB)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Carson Wentz (Mobile QB), Jordan Howard (RB), Nelson Agholor (WR)
Key Defensive Personnel: Brandon Graham (DE), Fletcher Cox (DT), Malik Jackson (DT), Zach Brown (OLB), Ronald Darby (CB), Malcolm Jenkins (SS)
Managers: Howie Roseman (GM), Doug Pederson (HC), Mike Groh (OC), Jim Schwartz (DC)
Vegas Win Total: 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-raiders/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 12:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-raiders/</guid>
      <description>Tier 7 QB: Derek Carr
Known Offensive Vectors: Jalen Richard (RB)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Tyrell Williams (WR), Josh Jacobs (RB), Doug Martin (RB)
Key Defensive Personnel: Clelin Ferrell (DE)
Managers: Mike Mayock (New GM), Jon Gruden (HC), Greg Olson (OC), Paul Guenther (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 6
Coaching Turnover:
Aside from the running backs coach, the offensive coaching staff has been kept intact from last year. It&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that this team has opted to keep Tom Cable around as the offensive line coach, despite his track record of failure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-chiefs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 12:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-chiefs/</guid>
      <description>Tier 1 QB: Patrick Mahomes
Known Offensive Vectors: Tyreek Hill (WR), Travis Kelce (TE)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Sammy Watkins (WR), Carlos Hyde (RB)
Key Defensive Personnel: Chris Jones (DT), Frank Clark (DE), Tyrann Mathieu (FS)
Managers: Brett Veach (GM), Andy Reid (HC), Eric Bieniemy (OC), Steve Spagnuolo (New DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 10.5
Coaching Turnover:
On offense, absolutely nothing has changed. A rarity in a league where assistant coaches typically travel around different teams every year or two.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-chargers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 12:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-chargers/</guid>
      <description>Tier 2 QB: Philip Rivers
Known Offensive Vectors: Keenan Allen (WR), Melvin Gordon (RB), Hunter Henry (TE)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Travis Benjamin (WR), Dontrelle Inman (WR)
Key Defensive Personnel: Joey Bosa (DE), Melvin Ingram (DE), Thomas Davis (LB), Casey Hayward (CB), Derwin James (SS)
Managers: Tom Telesco (GM), Anthony Lynn (HC), Ken Whisenhunt (OC), Gus Bradley (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 9.5
Coaching Turnover:
Remarkably, the coaching staff from last year has been almost wholly retained this season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-broncos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 12:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-broncos/</guid>
      <description>Tier 3 QB: Joe Flacco, Drew Lock
Known Offensive Vectors: Emmanuel Sanders (WR), Phillip Lindsay (RB)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Courtland Sutton (WR), Noah Fant (TE)
Key Defensive Personnel: Von Miller (DE), Bradley Chubb (DE), Chris Harris Jr. (CB), Bryce Callahan (CB), Derek Wolfe (DT)
Managers: John Elway (GM), Vic Fangio (New HC), Rich Scangarello (New OC), Ed Donatell (New DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 7
Coaching Turnover:
On offense, only the running backs coach and the wide receivers coach from last year managed to survive the transition from the short-lived Vance Joseph era to the Vic Fangio regime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-jaguars/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-jaguars/</guid>
      <description>Tier 3 QB: Nick Foles
Known Offensive Vectors: Keelan Cole (WR), Marqise Lee (WR)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Leonard Fournette (RB), Dede Westbrook (WR)
Key Defensive Personnel: Calais Campbell (E), Yannick Ngakoue (E), Marcel Dareus (DT), Josh Allen (OLB), Myles Jack (MLB), Telvin Smith (OLB), Jalen Ramsey (CB), A.J. Bouye (CB)
Managers: Tom Coughlin (Exec), David Caldwell (GM), Doug Marrone (HC), John DeFillippo (New OC), Todd Wash (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-texans/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 12:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-texans/</guid>
      <description>Tier 5 QB: Deshaun Watson
Known Offensive Vectors: DeAndre Hopkins (WR), Deshaun Watson (Mobile QB), Will Fuller (WR)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Duke Johnson (RB), Keke Coutee (WR), Kenny Stills (WR)
Key Defensive Personnel: J.J. Watt (DE), Whitney Mercilus (OLB), Benardrick McKinney (ILB)
Managers: Bill O’Brien (HC), Tim Kelly (New OC), Romeo Crennel (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 8.5
Staff Turnover
On the offensive end of things, Houston will now be shifting offensive coordinator duties away from Bill O’Brien.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-colts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 12:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-colts/</guid>
      <description>Tier 4 QB: Jacoby Brissett
Known Offensive Vectors: T.Y. Hilton (WR), Marlon Mack (RB)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Eric Ebron (TE), Devin Funchess (WR)
Notable Defensive Personnel: Jabaal Sheard (DT), Justin Houston (DE), Darius Leonard (OLB), Pierre Desir (CB)
Managers: Chris Ballard (GM), Frank Reich (HC), Nick Sirianni (OC), Matt Eberflus (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 9.5
Staff Turnover:
On the offensive side, we have a bit of turnover. The tight ends coach and the two offensive line coaches from last year were flipped for new folks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-titans/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 12:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-titans/</guid>
      <description>Tier 6 QB: Marcus Mariota, Ryan Tannehill (Backup)
Known Offensive Vectors: Derrick Henry (RB), Delanie Walker (TE)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Adam Humphries (WR), Marcus Mariota (Mobile QB), Dion Lewis (RB)
Key Defensive Personnel: Jurrell Casey (DE), Cameron Wake (OLB), Kevin Byard (SS), Adoree Jackson (CB)
Managers: Jon Robinson (GM), Mike Vrabels (HC), Arthur Smith (New OC), Dean Pees (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 8
Staff Turnover:
Despite Matt LeFleur’s departure for greener pastures in Wisconsin, the team managed to retain the rest of its offensive staff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-steelers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 12:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-steelers/</guid>
      <description>Tier 2 QB: Ben Roethlisberger
Known Offensive Vectors: Juju Smith-Schuster (WR), James Conner (RB)
Potential Offensive Vectors: James Washington (WR), Vance McDonald (TE), Donte Moncrief (WR)
Key Defensive Personnel: Cameron Heyward (DT), Stephon Tuitt (DE), T.J. Watt (OLB), Devin Bush (ILB), Steven Nelson (CB), Joe Haden (CB)
Managers: Kevin Colbert (GM), Mike Tomlin (HC), Randy Fichtner (OC), Keith Butler (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 9
Coaching Turnover:
On offense, only the running backs coach has been formally flipped during the offseason.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-browns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 12:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-browns/</guid>
      <description>Tier 4 QB: Baker Mayfield
Known Offensive Vectors: Odell Beckham (WR), Jarvis Landry (WR), Nick Chubb (RB), David Njoku (TE)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Duke Johnson (RB), Antonio Callaway (WR)
Key Defensive Personnel: Myles Garrett (DE), Olivier Vernon (DE), Denzel Ward (CB), Joe Schobert (MLB)
Managers: John Dorsey (GM), Freddie Kitchens (New HC), Todd Monken (New OC), Steve Wilks (New DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 9.5
Coaching Turnover:
A new head coach brings quite a few new faces to the coaching staff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-ravens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-ravens/</guid>
      <description>Tier 5 QB: Lamar Jackson
Known Offensive Vectors: Mark Ingram (RB), Lamar Jackson (Mobile QB), Mark Andrews (TE)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Alex Collins (RB), Marquise Brown (WR), Hayden Hurst (TE)
Key Defensive Personnel: Brandon Williams (DT), Matt Judon (DE), Earl Thomas (FS), Tony Jefferson (SS), Marlon Humphrey (CB)
Managers: Eric DeCosta (New GM), John Harbaugh (HC), Greg Roman (New OC), Don Martindale (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 8.5
Coaching Turnover:
On offense, we see quite a bit of reorganization this year now that Mornhinweg has been replaced with one of the main assistant coaches from last year, Greg Roman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-bengals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 12:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-bengals/</guid>
      <description>Tier 8 QB: Andy Dalton
Known Offensive Vectors: Tyler Boyd (WR), Joe Mixon (RB)
Potential Offensive Vectors: AJ Green (WR), Tyler Eifert (TE), C.J Uzomah (WR)
Key Defensive Personnel: Geno Atkins (DT), Carlos Dunlap (DE), Sam Hubbard (DE)
Managers: Mike Brown (GM/Owner), Zac Taylor (New HC), Brian Callahan (New OC), Lou Anaramo (New DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 6
Coaching Turnover:
I’m starting to notice a trend here. Even if a team goes through a coaching overhaul, the new head coach opts to keep certain position coaches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-patriots/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 12:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-patriots/</guid>
      <description>Tier 1 QB: Tom Brady
Known Offensive Vectors: Julian Edelman (WR), James White (RB), Sony Michel (RB), Antonio Brown (WR)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Josh Gordon (WR), Demaryius Thomas (WR), Cameron Meredith (WR), N’Keal Harry (WR)
Key Defensive Personnel: Michael Bennett (DE), Devin McCourty (FS), Patrick Chung (SS), Dont’a Hightower (LB), Kyle Van Noy (OLB), Stephon Gilmore (CB), Jamie Collins (OLB)
Managers: Bill Belichick (HC/GM), Josh McDaniels (OC), Greg Schiano Jerod Mayo (DC)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-dolphins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 12:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-dolphins/</guid>
      <description>Tier 8 QB: Josh Rosen, Ryan Fitzpatrick
Known Offensive Vectors: N/A
Potential Offensive Vectors: Kenyan Drake (RB), DeVante Parker (WR), Dwayne Allen (TE)
Key Defensive Personnel: Christian Wilkins (DT), Xavien Howard (CB)
Managers: Chris Grier (GM), Brian Flores (New HC), Chad O’Shea (New OC), Patrick Graham (New DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 4.5
Coaching Turnover:
On offense, only the running backs coach was spared from the inevitable overhaul that came when Brian Flores assumed head coaching duties following the firing of Adam Gase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-bills/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-bills/</guid>
      <description>Tier 6 QB: Josh Allen
Known Offensive Vectors: Josh Allen (Mobile QB), LeSean McCoy (RB), Zay Jones (WR)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Cole Beasley (WR), John Brown (WR), Tyler Kroft (WR)
Key Defensive Personnel: Lorenzo Alexander (OLB), Jerry Hughes (DE), Micah Hyde (SS), Tre’Davious White (CB)
Managers: Brandon Beane (GM), Sean McDermott (HC), Brian Daboll (OC), Leslie Frazier (DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 6.5
Coaching Turnover:
On offense, we actually see quite a bit of turnover here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-jets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/preseason-review-jets/</guid>
      <description>Tier 7 QB: Sam Darnold
Known Offensive Vectors: Robby Anderson (WR), Le’Veon Bell (RB)
Potential Offensive Vectors: Jamison Crowder (WR)
Key Defensive Personnel: Leonard Williams (DE), Quinnen Williams (DE), C.J. Mosley (LB), Jamal Adams (SS)
Managers: Joe Douglas (New GM), Adam Gase (New HC), Dowell Loggains (New OC), Gregg Williams (New DC)
Vegas Over/Under: 7
Coaching Turnover:
Nearly every single coach on the staff this year is new. Interestingly enough, only the two defensive back coaches from last year managed to survive the complete overhaul of the Jets organization this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/super-bowl-liii-prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2019 16:04:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/super-bowl-liii-prediction/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s all come down to this&amp;hellip;.the Los Angeles Rams versus the New England Patriots. What a shitty Super Bowl.
In the pieces I wrote recently on both teams, I&amp;rsquo;ve focused on a few things - the coaching and the pass rush. And I&amp;rsquo;ve come to one conclusion&amp;hellip;the Rams may have a slightly more talented team, but the Patriots are the more efficient team.
For Los Angeles to win, they need sensational performances from Aaron Donald and Ndamukong Suh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/rams-pass-rush-analysis-against-packers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 23:46:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/rams-pass-rush-analysis-against-packers/</guid>
      <description>One of the biggest factors determining which team wins in the Super Bowl is the pass rush. Almost always, the team with the better overall pass rush ends up hoisting the Lombardi trophy when the game is over. So let&amp;rsquo;s evaluate the overall efficacy of the Rams pass rush relative to the Patriots pass rush.
We do this by studying their games against common opponents. We look only for those common opponents that played both teams at roughly the same point in the season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/pats-pass-rush-against-packers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 23:32:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/pats-pass-rush-against-packers/</guid>
      <description>One of the biggest factors determining which team wins in the Super Bowl is the pass rush. Almost always, the team with the better overall pass rush ends up hoisting the Lombardi trophy when the game is over. So let&amp;rsquo;s evaluate the overall efficacy of the Patriots pass rush relative to the Rams pass rush.
We do this by studying their games against common opponents. We look only for those common opponents that played both teams at roughly the same point in the season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/patriots-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 18:53:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/patriots-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Rather than do quick statements discussing the Patriots and their victory over Kansas City to retain possession of the AFC crown&amp;hellip;I&amp;rsquo;ll be doing a deep dive here in order to more correctly illustrate the strengths and weaknesses of this New England team as they head into the Super Bowl.
1st Quarter The first play of the day sets the tone for the Patriots on offense. Against a seven-man box, Sony Michel still manages to chew off 11 yards behind some excellent blocks by his offensive linemen, his fullback James Develin, and tight end Rob Gronkowski.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/rams-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 13:11:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/rams-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Rather than list bullet points quickly explaining the Rams victory in the NFC championship game, I&amp;rsquo;ll be doing a deep dive, keeping notes here as I watch coaches&amp;rsquo; film of the game.
1st Quarter The Saints started out hot, thanks to a smartly executed tight-end screen, Alvin Kamara running wheel routes, and Michael Thomas making catches against tight coverage.
Still&amp;hellip;there were indications the Saints&amp;rsquo; success would be a little unsustainable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/patriots-chiefs-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 23:31:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/patriots-chiefs-preview/</guid>
      <description>The New England Patriots meet the Kansas City Chiefs at Arrowhead Stadium for the AFC Championship game.
The Patriots have underwhelmed this year compared to years past. On the road this season, the team has only managed three wins. And frankly, only one of those victories came against a quality team.
While the Patriots were able to beat the Chiefs in the regular season, that was a home game against Patrick Mahomes early in the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/rams-saints-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 22:13:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/rams-saints-preview/</guid>
      <description>The NFC championship will be the Los Angeles Rams visiting the New Orleans Saints in a rematch from the regular-season.
The Rams finally adjusted and began running the ball more, this time with CJ Anderson as the lead halfback. Gurley was the better rusher last week on a yards-per-rush basis, but CJ Anderson was without doubt the team&amp;rsquo;s bell cow in the run game. And Anderson will need to go off again for his team to have any hope of winning in a hostile Superdome this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/on-road-teams-in-the-playoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 21:46:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/on-road-teams-in-the-playoffs/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m beginning to realize that road teams need to be truly stacked if they&amp;rsquo;re going to be making a run in the postseason. Road teams need an elite quarterback, at least 3 different weapons on offense, and at least 2 stud pass rushers. Quality coaching is a necessity as well, but coaches can only work with the resources they&amp;rsquo;re given.
So anything less than that and a road team will see its offense eventually stalled or its defense eventually victimized in the postseason.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/saints-over-eagles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 20:05:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/saints-over-eagles/</guid>
      <description>The Saints have bested the defending champions and have one more game to play before their trip to the Super Bowl. But first a couple thoughts&amp;hellip;
 In the 3rd quarter, the Saints sustained a drive that lasted 11 and a half minutes. 11 and a half fucking minutes. It was amazing. It was a grueling crawl down the field, but the Saints were finally able to punch one past the goal line after 18 plays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/patriots-over-chargers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 15:11:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/patriots-over-chargers/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s only halftime, but the Patriots are going to win this one. The game was over by the 2-minute warning in the first half.
 The Patriots are once again putting on a coaching clinic here. New England saw Los Angeles&amp;rsquo; putting smaller bodies out there to defend the flat and decided that these smaller defenders would have trouble handling crushing runs right up the middle.
 Outside of a single batted pass, Ingram and Bosa have been blanked in the first half.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/eagles-saints-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 11:33:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/eagles-saints-preview/</guid>
      <description>The Philadelphia Eagles return to New Orleans in their quest to repeat as champions.
The Eagles do not deserve to be such crazy underdogs in this match-up. I know, I know Philadelphia was shellacked earlier in the year when these two teams met in the Superdome&amp;hellip;but the postseason is different from the regular season. In the regular season, teams ebb and flow. And the Eagles were clearly trending down that week while the Saints were staking their claim as the cream of the crop in the NFC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/chargers-patriots-playoff-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 01:38:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/chargers-patriots-playoff-preview/</guid>
      <description>The Chargers fly again to the east coast this weekend, this time to contend against the New England Patriots.
The Chargers nearly have a complete team. And it puts them in position to pull off an upset here. New England can still win this game, but it will not be easy. Los Angeles comes into this game with the superior pass rush, headlined by Melvin Ingram and Joey Bosa. I expect Tom Brady to be harangued regularly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/rams-over-cowboys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 00:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/rams-over-cowboys/</guid>
      <description>Some thoughts on the Rams first playoff win in the Sean McVay era&amp;hellip;
 Finally, the Rams have returned to their old successful ways from earlier in the season. With a healthier Todd Gurley and CJ Anderson finally brought up to speed on McVay&amp;rsquo;s playbook, Los Angeles was able to pound the ball on the turf for 273 yards.
 Being able to run the ball also opened up that other thing McVay loves to call - the crossing routes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/chiefs-over-colts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 20:09:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/chiefs-over-colts/</guid>
      <description>Just a few points to make about the Chiefs and their division round victory over the Colts.
 Any doubts I may have had about the Chiefs&amp;rsquo; championship prospects have been quieted. All 3 of their star pass rushers made their presence known throughout the game. Mahomes played with some admirable composure in his first real postseason game. The running game came back alive behind Damien Williams. If the run game stays alive, Kansas City is easily the most complete team alive in the postseason.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/cowboys-rams-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 17:57:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/cowboys-rams-preview/</guid>
      <description>The Ladyboys travel to Los Angeles to face off against the second-seeded Rams.
The Rams are justifiably the favorites here. In all categories outside of coaching and home field advantage, the Cowboys manage draw even against Los Angeles. But it&amp;rsquo;s that latter exception that should concern Dallas. Jason Garrett is still a questionable coach, especially on the road. His refusal to incorporate his quarterback&amp;rsquo;s mobility into his offense is idiotic. The Cowboys desperately need another dimension of offense early in the year, but Garrett and offensive coordinator Scott Linehan simply refused to leverage the speed of their Dak Prescott&amp;rsquo;s running ability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/colts-chiefs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 22:31:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/colts-chiefs/</guid>
      <description>An exciting rematch of a thriller from not too long ago, when Andrew Luck staged one of the greatest postseason comebacks in history.
So this is a very interesting match. Both teams have distinct advantages over one another. The Chiefs are rolling into the contest with 3 elite pass rushers and home field advantage. The Colts, meanwhile, come to Arrowhead Stadium with the more experienced quarterback and a more dynamic offense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/eagles-over-bears/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 21:35:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/eagles-over-bears/</guid>
      <description>Some quick points&amp;hellip;
 Incredibly hard-fought match. I would say Matt Nagy out-coached Doug Pederson here. Lining Allen Robinson up over cornerback Avonte Maddox and having him run double moves on the young defensive back yielded big gains in the pass game. The Eagles took a little too long to fix that issue.
 Mitch Trubisky handled his nerves well. He threw two bad throws early on that should have been picked if the Eagles&amp;rsquo; cornerbacks were just a bit more sure-handed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/chargers-over-ravens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:58:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/chargers-over-ravens/</guid>
      <description>Some quick points&amp;hellip;
 For once, I was right on the money with my quick little analysis. Lamar Jackson&amp;rsquo;s inexperience held him back for most of the game.
 More importantly, the Chargers drafted a much better game plan in this rematch. Los Angeles dedicated so many more defensive resources to the run this time around. The SuperChargers were daring the Ravens to throw the ball and Lamar Jackson simply shriveled up under the postseason spotlight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/revised-wild-card-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 01:10:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/revised-wild-card-picks/</guid>
      <description>So the first two games are done and I&amp;rsquo;m technically 1-1. While I was horrifically off in my assessment of the Colts-Texans game, the Seahawks managed to cover the spread in the last minutes of the game. But in all honesty, I deserve to be 0-2. Had the Seahawks not lost their kicker to injury at the end of the first half, Seattle would likely have lost by 3 points instead of 2 points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/cowboys-over-seahawks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 23:18:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/cowboys-over-seahawks/</guid>
      <description>Just a few points to make about the Cowboys win over the Seahawks&amp;hellip;
 If the definition of insanity is doing something over and over again expecting different results&amp;hellip;then the Seahawks offensive game plan is the quintessential example of insanity. Constantly running the ball up the middle of this Seahawks defense did not work was nothing but exercises in futility.  - * Dallas had the more dynamic offense here. The Cowboys involved were able to incorporate receivers other than Amari Cooper into the offensive game plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/colts-over-texans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 19:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/colts-over-texans/</guid>
      <description>Several quick points to make here&amp;hellip;.
 Bill O&amp;rsquo;Brien is a terrible coach. Too many times, I saw Indianapolis had a beat on the Texans&amp;rsquo; offensive schemes before the snap. Honestly, the Colts knew Houston&amp;rsquo;s playbook better than some of Houston&amp;rsquo;s own skill players.
 Penalties. The Texans committed too many sloppy pre-snap penalties, two of which sustained drives that led to Colt touchdowns. Not only are these players stupid for drawing these penalties, but Houston&amp;rsquo;s coaching bears some blame here for letting these guys play so undisciplined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/wild-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 00:27:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/wild-card/</guid>
      <description>Colts @ Texans (-1) Loving the Texans here. The Texans are the team with more talent, more playoff experience, and home field advantage. Houston should win rather commandingly here.
Pick: Texans (ML)
Seahawks @ Cowboys (-2.5) Both teams are roughly even on defense. However, the Cowboys are playing with home field advantage, whereas the Seahawks come into this contest with an elite quarterback and a more dynamic offense. Not quite certain what will play a bigger role in this game, but the Seahawks carry another advantage over the Cowboys here - coaching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/playoff-analysis-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 23:14:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/playoff-analysis-2018/</guid>
      <description> So I analyzed all 12 playoff teams and assessed their chances of making the Super Bowl.
Click on any of the team logos below to navigate to the write-up for that particular team.
NFC Playoffs               AFC Playoffs               </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/patriots-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 13:20:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/patriots-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>The dynasty team finds its way into the playoffs yet again, this time as the second seed in the American Football Conference.
Quarterback: Tom Brady One year removed from being crowned the league MVP, Tom Brady is still very much an elite player. That being said, his play has regressed a bit. His deep ball accuracy percentage sunk downward from 46.5% to 43%. His passing yards per attempt has dropped by about three-tenths of a yard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/rams-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 11:36:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/rams-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>The Rams stumbled for a bit, but finally righted the ship at the end of the season to claim the second seed in the National Football Conference.
Quarterback: Jared Goff Some were making the case early in the season that Goff deserves serious MVP consideration. That case quickly went to shit after the Rams returned from their bye week. With defenses finally having decoded the Rams offensive scheme and Gurley banged up, Goff was largely left up to his own devices to create plays on the fly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/chiefs-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 17:13:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/chiefs-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>The Chiefs have emerged from nowhere and seized the top seed in the American Football Conference, thanks largely to the future MVP playing at quarterback - Patrick Mahomes.
Quarterback: Patrick Mahomes As the prospective MVP of the season, there&amp;rsquo;s no question Patrick Mahomes is an elite quarterback.
Offensive Weapons: Tyreek Hill, Travis Kelce Tyreek Hill and Travis Kelce were spectacular last year, but even better this year now that a truly elite quarterback was at the helm of the offense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/saints-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 00:23:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/saints-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>New Orleans returns back to the postseason after a painful loss against the Vikings last year in the division round. The Saints stand as the top seed in the National Football Conference.
Quarterback: Drew Brees Drew Brees is an MVP candidate for a reason. Yes, a few of his games this season have been completely ordinary. But the eye test and the statistics irrefutably validates his status as an elite quarterback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/texans-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 00:07:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/texans-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Deshaun Watson&amp;rsquo;s return from ACL injury started out a little sloppy, to be honest. But once the team finally settled into a rhythm, the team won 11 of their last 14 contests, which netted them the 3rd seed in the American Football Conference.
Quarterback: Deshaun Watson The man truly earned his stripes this season. For much of the season, Watson was forced to play without much talent in the receiver position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/colts-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 15:00:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/colts-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>The Steelers slipping out of playoff contention allowed the Indianapolis Colts to work their way into the postseason as the sixth seed of the American Football Conference. How far will Andrew Luck go in his comeback year?
Quarterback: Andrew Luck Luck will win the Comeback Player of the Year award. Nothing else needs to be said. Under Frank Reich, Luck has not only regained his old form, but adopted a quick release into his passing style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/eagles-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 23:49:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/eagles-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>With a little help from the Bears, the Eagles have slipped back into the playoffs as the bottom seed in the National Football Conference. Will Nick&amp;rsquo;s BD work its magic again this year?
Quarterback: Nick Foles / Nate Sudfeld Nick Foles seems like an elite quarterback. Watching film from yesterday&amp;rsquo;s game against the Redskins, I saw him looking off zone defenders, taking whatever opportunities were available to him, and throwing the ball with a little touch in order to hit his receivers in stride.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/bears-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 01:38:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/bears-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Under Matt Nagy, the Chicago Bears have gone from being considered the dregs of the NFC North division to being crowned the Kings of the North. Chicago is now locked in as the third seed of the National Football Conference.
Quarterback: Mitchell Trubisky Mitch sucks. Not only is he horribly inaccurate, but some keen-eyed analysts have observed that the kid may simply be incapable of throwing the ball to the left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/seahawks-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/seahawks-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>The Seattle Seahawks are locked into the fifth seed of the National Football Conference. Pretty amazing feat given their low preseason expectations&amp;hellip;
Quarterback: Russell Wilson Russell Wilson has been up and down this season. His performance against the Chiefs last week was a throwback to the last couple years when he was undoubtedly an elite quarterback. But then watch his game against the Vikings and doubts begin to creep up on whether he&amp;rsquo;s losing his touch&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/ravens-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 20:59:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/ravens-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>The Baltimore Ravens have stamped their ticket to the American Football Conference playoffs as the 4th seed. With Lamar Jackson at the helm of the offense, the Ravens are one of the more intriguing teams playing in the postseason.
Quarterback: Lamar Jackson As I&amp;rsquo;ll discuss at length in the next section, Lamar Jackson has been a jolt his team desperately needed after Joe Flacco went down with injury. But when it comes to executing on quarterbacking fundamentals&amp;hellip;the man disappoints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/chargers-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 00:28:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/chargers-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>The ~Los Angeles~ San Diego Chargers have claimed the 5th seed in the American Football Conference playoffs. Despite a crummy home field advantage, the Bolts have rode high on some MVP-quality play from Philip Rivers.
Quarterback: Philip Rivers As I said before, Philip Rivers has played like an elite quarterback. There&amp;rsquo;s a reason his name has been thrown about in MVP discussions.
Offensive Weapons: Keenan Allen, Melvin Gordon It feels odd that the Chargers only have two solid offensive skill players, despite all their success in the passing game this season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/cowboys-playoff-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2018 19:04:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/cowboys-playoff-analysis/</guid>
      <description>The Dallas Cowboys are officially the 4th seed in the National Football Conference playoffs. Jerry Jones and the Clapper will be leading their men into the postseason, starting Wild Card weekend with a home showing against the Seahawks (most likely).
Quarterback: Dak Prescott Dak Prescott is not an elite quarterback. All of the strengths we associate with top-tier quarterbacks - accuracy, decision-making, composure under pressure, efficiency&amp;hellip;none of these are traits that can be associated with Dak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving Bonanza!</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/thanksgiving-bonanza/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 22:08:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/thanksgiving-bonanza/</guid>
      <description>My favorite holiday of the year. Not because of the turkey or the food or anything, fuck that. It&amp;rsquo;s all about having the day off to make bets on three consecutive primetime football games.
Let&amp;rsquo;s look through each game and find some bets to like. I feel good about these slate of games too.
Chicago Bears @ Detroit Lions (+2.5) (Point Total: 43.5) The spread cleared below the key number of 3 earlier today as word finally got around that Mitch Trubisky was highly unlikely to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviewing Atlanta&#39;s Loss Against the Cowboys</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/reviewing-atlanta-s-loss-against-the-cowboys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 22:11:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/reviewing-atlanta-s-loss-against-the-cowboys/</guid>
      <description>To nudge myself out of the funk I was in Sunday night, when I barely missed hitting a lucrative five-team parlay (may the gods smite Kirk Cousins for the rest of his life), I decided to review game tape from the Falcons loss to the Cowboys earlier in the day.
Two major takeaways&amp;hellip;
 Matt Ryan found himself flustered by Dallas&amp;rsquo; pass rush, especially when they blitzed. His worst throws of the day came against blitzes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 11 - Risky Propositions</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-11-risky-propositions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 14:07:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-11-risky-propositions/</guid>
      <description>In this series, I&amp;rsquo;ll details bets that are a little risky for my blood.
Panthers @ Lions Such a beautiful spot for the Lions here. Coming off three embarrassing losses, Detroit is primed to play better now that they&amp;rsquo;ve returned back home and their season is on the line. And last week&amp;rsquo;s game against Chicago shows me that the team can defend against the run when it&amp;rsquo;s a central focus of their defensive game plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 11 Best Bets</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-11-best-bets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 21:58:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-11-best-bets/</guid>
      <description>All right, so the Supercontest is a lost cause. I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure I&amp;rsquo;m treading water at exactly 50%. Statistically, I&amp;rsquo;m no better than a coin. A fucking coin.
But at the very least, each season offers up lessons for me to internalize. I like to believe I improve as a bettor every year. To be honest though, my best year as a sports gambler has been the first year I&amp;rsquo;ve actually started wagering serious money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 10 Bets</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-10-bets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 14:52:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-10-bets/</guid>
      <description>Good week last week from a betting perspective, even if two of my Supercontest picks were losers. A superteaser hit landed me a pretty penny. Anyway&amp;hellip;
Saints (-6) @ Bengals Give me the Saints all day long.
The Bengals biggest problem on offense has always been that they lack reliable weapons that have won over the trust of their quarterback, Andy Dalton. And now you tell me his most trusted receiver in AJ Green is out?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bucs @ Panthers - Some Quick Game Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/bucs-panthers-some-quick-game-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 20:58:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/bucs-panthers-some-quick-game-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Just some real quick analysis&amp;hellip;.
The Panthers played phenomenal here, much to my surprise. And yet, a part of me still has questions of whether the Panthers are actually a legitimate playoff threat.
Their success in the last game was predicated on two things - devilishly creative play-calling and an eagerness to blitz against an offense that has absolutely no ability to read an incoming blitz.
Don&amp;rsquo;t believe me? Well, let me show you a few plays that stood out to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 9 - Sunday Night Football</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-9-sunday-night-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 18:00:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-9-sunday-night-football/</guid>
      <description>Packers (+5) @ Patriots Listen, it&amp;rsquo;s always risky betting against the Patriots, but their defense is a little too tepid for my liking. The Packers will cover so long as Bill Belichick&amp;rsquo;s defense fail to keep Aaron Rodger&amp;rsquo;s receivers bottled up under man coverage. As I keep saying, the Packers can be routed so long as you have a defensive secondary that can hold up well in man-to-man defense. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have such a secondary, expect Rodgers to run up some scores on you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 9 - Best Bets</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-9-best-bets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 23:43:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-9-best-bets/</guid>
      <description>My best bets of the week. Last week, I went 2-3. Two of those three losses came courtesy of the Chiefs and Rams failing to cover their spreads. BAH! I would not consider either of those picks to be terrible&amp;hellip;but it is pretty clear neither team deserved to cover their respective spreads last week. And this week, I will be rooting against one of them to flat out lose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 8 Review</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-8-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 22:26:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-8-review/</guid>
      <description>My Supercontest picks sucked this week.
Not really too interested in dwelling too much on why my selections didn&amp;rsquo;t pan out, although I do want to give a bit of a breakdown of the Kansas City/Denver game.
As I expected, Kansas City would post at least 30 points. But what took me by surprise was Case Keenum. Arrowhead Stadium is usually the place where bad quarterbacks go to finally die. Just look at Blake Bortles and his downfall following his poor showing in Arrowhead earlier in the season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 8 - Early Leanings</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-8-early-leanings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 20:12:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-8-early-leanings/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 7 - Early Leanings</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-7-early-leanings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 22:57:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-7-early-leanings/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>49ers @ Packers - Quick Look</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/49ers-packers-quick-look/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 20:01:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/49ers-packers-quick-look/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rams-Broncos Halftime Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/rams-broncos-halftime-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 17:43:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/rams-broncos-halftime-analysis/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colts @ Jets - Halftime Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/colts-jets-halftime-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 14:26:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/colts-jets-halftime-analysis/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 5 Picks</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-5-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 22:30:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-5-picks/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 4 Picks</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-4-picks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 00:25:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/week-4-picks/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction...</title>
      <link>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 22:24:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.owlpicks.com/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>